Processing bank 0
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:30 is the same as 0:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:31 is the same as 0:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:51 is the same as 0:50!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:52 is the same as 0:50!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:53 is the same as 0:50!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:56 is the same as 0:55!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:8c is the same as 0:6c!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:8d is the same as 0:6d!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:8e is the same as 0:6e!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:8f is the same as 0:6f!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:91 is the same as 0:3!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:95 is the same as 0:3!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:9d is the same as 0:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:b1 is the same as 0:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:c3 is the same as 0:3!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:ce is the same as 0:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:cf is the same as 0:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 0:f6 is the same as 0:5d!
Processing bank 1
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:2 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:3 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:4 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:5 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:6 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:7 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:b is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:15 is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:16 is the same as 1:14!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:17 is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:19 is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:1a is the same as 1:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:1c is the same as 1:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:1d is the same as 1:1b!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:1e is the same as 1:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:1f is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:24 is the same as 1:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:26 is the same as 1:14!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:27 is the same as 1:21!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:29 is the same as 1:21!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:2a is the same as 1:28!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:2b is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:2d is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:2f is the same as 1:21!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:30 is the same as 1:28!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:31 is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:34 is the same as 1:28!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:35 is the same as 1:1b!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:36 is the same as 1:14!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:37 is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:39 is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:3b is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:3d is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:3e is the same as 1:38!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:3f is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:40 is the same as 1:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:41 is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:42 is the same as 1:10!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:43 is the same as 1:11!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:47 is the same as 1:45!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:4c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:4d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:4e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:4f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:50 is the same as 1:2c!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:51 is the same as 1:21!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:52 is the same as 1:28!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:53 is the same as 1:21!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:57 is the same as 1:55!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:5c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:5d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:5e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:5f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:60 is the same as 1:3c!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:61 is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:62 is the same as 1:14!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:63 is the same as 1:25!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:67 is the same as 1:65!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:69 is the same as 1:65!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:6a is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:6c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:6d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:6e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:6f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:70 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:71 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:72 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:73 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:74 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:76 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:77 is the same as 1:75!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:79 is the same as 1:75!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:7c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:7d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:7e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:7f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:80 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:81 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:82 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:83 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:84 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:85 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:86 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:87 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:88 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:89 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8a is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8b is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:8f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:90 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:91 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:92 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:93 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:94 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:95 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:96 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:97 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:98 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:99 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9a is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9b is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9c is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9d is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9e is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:9f is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a0 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a1 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a2 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a3 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a4 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a5 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a6 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a7 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a8 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:a9 is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:aa is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:ab is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:ac is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:ad is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:ae is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:af is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:bb is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:bc is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:bd is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:be is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:bf is the same as 1:0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:c5 is the same as 1:c3!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:c6 is the same as 1:c0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:c7 is the same as 1:c1!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:c8 is the same as 1:c0!
Duplicate tile found: tile 1:c9 is the same as 1:c3!
